<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on ECR Cluster Documentation Site</title>
    <link>https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on ECR Cluster Documentation Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 16:35:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cluster</title>
      <link>https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/the-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/the-cluster/</guid>
      <description>The Cluster The cluster is made up of 1 head node and 10 compute nodes. Of the compute nodes, 8 are AMD based systems while the other 2 are Intel based systems. Here is the following hardware stack for all of the nodes:
   Node Type Node Name Processor RAM HDD (/tmp) Extra Components     Head Node robotarium AMD Opteron 6320 (8 cores) 64 GB 916 GB &amp;mdash;   AMD Compute Node gpu01, gpu02, gpu03, gpu04, gpu05, gpu06 4x AMD Opteron 6376 (64 cores) 512 GB 40 GB NVIDIA K20 GPU, (2x in gpu06)   AMD Compute Node (Large RAM) gpu07, gpu08 4x AMD Opteron 6376 (64 cores) 1024 GB 40 GB NVIDIA K20 GPU (only in gpu07), 2x NVIDIA Titan Xp GPUs (only in gpu08)   Intel Compute Node mic01, mic02 2x Intel Xeon E5-2650v2 (16 cores) 128 GB 40 GB &amp;mdash;   NVIDIA DGX1 Node dgx01 2x Intel Xeon E5-2698v4 (40 cores) 512 GB 440 GB (7 TB at /raid/scratch) 8x NVIDIA Tesla P100    In addition to the above listed nodes, there are also some special-purpose nodes &amp;mdash; specifically, the cluster has eight Intel MIC nodes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To</title>
      <link>https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 16:35:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/how-to/</guid>
      <description>How To Here we provide some guides for various aspects of using the Robotarium cluster. The most important ones are listed directly below &amp;mdash; it is a good idea to familiarise yourselves with these first. Please be aware that some of the guides here are hosted on other sites and will need you to navigate away from here.
Note: this page is still being populated, if you feel that anything is missing or amiss please contact us and we&amp;rsquo;ll update this page appropriately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 16:19:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ecr-cluster.github.io/docs/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Quick Start This guide provides a quick-n-dirty series of steps to get you started on the cluster. The guides assumes the following:
 you have an account on the cluster you have experience with Linux-based systems (especially the command line) you have a SSH public-private key pair  Alright then, lift off!
Accessing the Cluster (SSH) TBC</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>